http://www.william-powell.co.uk/security-and-privacy/

PRIVACY POLICY
William Powell Ltd is part of a group of businesses that also includes JM Osborne & Co Ltd and William Powell Sporting Ltd. This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.
TOPICS
What information do we collect about you?
How will we use the information about you?
Marketing Access to your information and correction
Cookies
Other websites
Changes to our privacy policy
How to contact us
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?
We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide product/service feedback and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.
HOW WILL WE USE THE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU?
We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to contact you about other products and services we think may be of interest to you. We use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website. If you agree, we shall pass on your personal information to our group of companies so that they may offer you their products and services. We will not share your information for marketing purposes with companies outside our three businesses. In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies. We do not store credit card details. It’s important we listen to our customers through their feedback in order to allow us to develop the William Powell proposition to deliver better service and products. We use a company called Feefo to gather independent reviews of both our service and our products and you can choose whether to do so or not.
MARKETING
We would like to send you information about products and services of ours and our other businesses which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to our other businesses. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please contact us via whichever method is most convenient for you.
ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND CORRECTION
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email us at info@williampowell.com or write to us at William Powell Ltd, Carrs House, Tramway, Banbury, Oxon, OX16 5TD. We may make a small charge for this service. We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
COOKIES
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information visit aboutcookies.org or allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.
OTHER WEBSITES
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 5th April 2018 and was created referencing the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) best practice examples as at this date.
HOW TO CONTACT US
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
by email info@williampowell.com
or write to us at: William Powell Ltd, Carrs House, Tramway, Banbury, Oxon, OX16 5TD
×
